<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skin_Scanner_App</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_needed">Camera permission is needed to use this feature.</string>

<!--    Recommendations tab   -->
    <string name="recommendations_title">Recommendations to Reduce Skin Cancer Risk</string>
    <string name="protect_skin_title">Protect Your Skin From UV Rays:</string>
    <string name="protect_skin_tips">
        • Stay in the shade during peak UV hours (10 a.m. to 4 p.m.).\n
        • Wear protective clothing like long sleeves, pants, and wide-brimmed hats.\n
        • Use sunglasses with UVA and UVB protection to shield your eyes.\n
        • Apply sunscreen: Use a broad-spectrum SPF 30+ sunscreen (preferably SPF 50) and reapply every 2 hours.
    </string>
    <string name="uv_index_title">Understand the UV Index:</string>

    <string name="uv_index_clickable">Check the daily UV Index for your area.</string>
    <string name="uv_index_text"> If it’s 3 or higher, take extra precautions to protect your skin.</string>

    <string name="avoid_uv_title">Avoid Artificial UV Exposure:</string>
    <string name="avoid_uv_tips">
        • Skip tanning beds, booths, and sunlamps. These devices emit high levels of UV rays, increasing the risk of skin cancer.\n
        • A tan is a sign of skin damage, not health. Even a “base tan” can harm your skin.
    </string>
    <string name="sun_safety_title">General Sun Safety Tips:</string>
    <string name="sun_safety_tips">
        • Stay hydrated: Drink plenty of water when outdoors.\n
        • Use shade creatively: Umbrellas, trees, and shelters can help reduce UV exposure.\n
        • Teach children sun safety: Start early with sunscreen and protective clothing to instill good habits.
    </string>
    <string name="end_of_day_title">End-of-Day Skin Care:</string>
    <string name="end_of_day_tips">
    • Apply a gentle moisturizer: Rehydrate your skin after cleansing to help restore its natural barrier and lock in moisture. Look for moisturizers with soothing ingredients like aloe vera, hyaluronic acid, or ceramides.\n
    • Avoid harsh chemicals: Choose alcohol-free and fragrance-free products to prevent irritation.\n
    • Focus on damaged areas: If your skin feels dry, red, or irritated from sun exposure, use a calming lotion designed for after-sun care.\n
    • Hydrate internally: Drink plenty of water throughout the day to keep your skin hydrated from within.
</string>
    <string name="skin_damage_title">Signs of Skin Damage:</string>
    <string name="skin_damage_tips">
        Any redness, tanning, or burning is a sign of skin injury. Even slight tanning can lead to long-term damage. Watch for new or unusual moles and consult a dermatologist if you notice changes.
    </string>
    <string name="source_title">Source:</string>
    <string name="source_link_text">CDC: Skin Cancer Prevention</string>


<!--    Hospitals   -->
    <string name="hospitals_title">Find Health Centers nearby</string>
    <string name="hospitals_description_text">If you are concerned about the spot on your skin or received scan results you can click the button to search for the nearest health centers</string>
    <string name="find_nearby_health_centers">Find nearby \n</string>

</resources>